{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_Kolb",
    "predicate": "property/prizes",
    "object": "Oersted Medal",
    "human_readable": "Edward Kolb has been awarded the Oersted Medal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833909273147583,
            "question": "For what accomplishment was Edward Kolb awarded the Oersted Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9147213101387024,
            "question": "Who has been awarded the Oersted Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621779680252075,
            "question": "What prestigious award did Edward Kolb receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7042736411094666,
            "question": "Can you name other notable recipients of the Oersted Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5343807339668274,
            "question": "What is the significance of receiving the Oersted Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.504025399684906,
            "question": "What does the Oersted Medal recognize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44738298654556274,
            "question": "What are some of Edward Kolb's major contributions to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.439800888299942,
            "question": "What field is the Oersted Medal associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42418259382247925,
            "question": "How does receiving the Oersted Medal impact an individual's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41715240478515625,
            "question": "Is Edward Kolb known for his work in physics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward Kolb has been awarded the Oersted Medal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4141_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does receiving the Oersted Medal impact an individual's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4141_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is the Oersted Medal associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4141_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Edward Kolb's major contributions to science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4141_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4141_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can tell that you're asking about a triple related to Edward Kolb and the Oersted Medal. However, Edward Kolb is mentioned in one of the documents as being awarded the Quantrell Award for Excellence in Undergraduate Teaching and the Oersted Medal is mentioned in several other documents, but it's not explicitly stated that Edward Kolb has been awarded this medal.\n\nSince there's no explicit information about Edward Kolb receiving the Oersted Medal in any of the provided documents, I would say:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document containing \"35.txt\" explicitly mentions that Edward Kolb was awarded the Oersted Medal, supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\nBased on the context information provided, it is mentioned that Edward Kolb was awarded the Quantrell Award for Excellence in Undergraduate Teaching and the Oersted Medal of the American Association of Physics Teachers. Thus, the statement \"Edward Kolb has been awarded the Oersted Medal\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information provided details about the Oersted Medal, its criteria (outstanding impact on teaching physics), and past recipients. Edward Kolb's achievements described focus on research, authorship of textbooks and popular science books on cosmology, and contributions to particle physics and cosmology. There's no mention of his work directly impacting physics education or receiving the Oersted Medal.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Edward Kolb being awarded the Oersted Medal in any part of the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}